hiphopstan.com 2011-11-24

# Privacy Policy | HipHopStan.com

HipHopStan, LLC respects your privacy. This privacy policy is part of the Terms of Service. This policy notifies you of:  
  
What personally identifiable information of yours is collected from you through our Website, the organization collecting the information, how the information is used, with whom the information may be shared, what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information, the kind of procedures we employ in an effort to hinder the unauthorized access, deletion, alteration, use or disclosure of information you provide to HipHopStan, LLC, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information you provide to us. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us via email at [privacypolicy@hiphopstan.com](mailto:privacypolicy@hiphopstan.com).

 **Scope of Policy  
**  
This policy applies to HipHopStan’s treatment of personally identifiable information that HipHopStan collects through HipHopStan’s website (the “Website”) and when you use HipHopStan’s services offered via the Website. The policy does not apply to practices of companies whose sites may be linked to the Website. For access to the privacy policies of such linked sites please refer to the information provided by such sites at their home pages. Also see the paragraph below under the heading “Hypertext Links.”  
  
**How do we use the information we collect.**  
  
HipHopStan collects personally identifiable information when you request information from HipHopStan. On such occasions, HipHopStan asks for your name, email address, phone number, zip code and personal information concerning your interests, occupation, gender and other demographic information. HipHopStan also receives and records information from server logs from your browser, including “cookie” information (as described below) relating to pages requested and the like.  
  
HipHopStan does not seek to collect such information from persons under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any such information to us. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under the age of 13 who has provided such information to us, please inform us (through the Website or via the email address listed above) and we will remove such information from our database as described further below.

In addition, no person (of any age) is required to provide us with the personally identifiable information we request. If you do not wish to provide such information, you are free not to do so. Your provision of requested information to us through our Website or other means is presumed by us to be voluntary and with your consent to the uses described herein. If after submitting personally identifiable information to us, you wish to “opt-out,” please contact us as noted above and we will remove your information from our database as set forth below in the section titled “Managing Your Information.” Please know that such a decision will not stop advertising or content that is generated prior to the time when we remove your information.  
  
HipHopStan uses the information you provide to us to customize advertising and content that we present to you, to contact you concerning specials and new products and to enhance our product offerings. HipHopStan will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party except when:

You have been given an opportunity to “opt out” of sharing the information and have declined to exercise that right within the time period provided;  
  
HipHopStan must share the information in order to provide a product or service that you have requested, in which case we will demand that any third party we use to fulfill your order agree that it does not have the right to use the personally identifiable information for any reason other than to fulfill your request; or  
  
HipHopStan, LLC is required to respond to subpoena, court orders or other legal process requiring such disclosure.  
  
In addition, we may share your information with our strategic partners and other third parties with whom we have a written agreement that provides for a cooperative, mutually beneficial commercial relationship. In these cases, we may not give you notice or an opportunity to opt out, but we will obligate that third party to treat your information as confidential, and not to use it for any purposes other than those for which we are authorized to use it.  
  
**Use of Cookies  
**  
HipHopStan uses cookies to enhance the interactive nature of your Internet experience and to provide a convenient feature to save you time. Cookies enable HipHopStan to quickly retrieve specific information from previous visits and to recall features that you may have customized on your browser.  
  
**Managing Your Information  
**  
You are entitled to request access to and correction of all your personal data collected by us via this Website, as well as to require us to delete your data if you no longer want us to process it. You can make such a request or a related inquiry by contacting us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to remove your information promptly after we receive your request. For contact information, email info@hiphopstan.com. Please note that there may be a small charge for making an access request or it may be free, depending on the circumstances. You can find out more details by emailing or calling us as provided above. We will keep your data as long as it is reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. You may choose not to receive unsolicited marketing material from HipHopStan and you have the right to request deletion of your HipHopStan account information, subject to HipHopStan’s need to keep appropriate archives of its business operations.  
  
**Security  
**  
HipHopStan employs reasonable measures to maintain all personally identifiable information provided by you on computer servers in a controlled and secured environment in an effort to hinder unauthorized access, loss, alteration, use or disclosure of such information. However, the nature of the Internet is such that information may be transmitted over networks without appropriate security measures and may be accessed, deleted, altered, used or disclosed by unauthorized persons.  
  
Because of the international nature of the services and products provided by this Website and the nature of HipHopStan Digital’s business, personal data may, subject to applicable law, be transferred internationally throughout HipHopStan’s worldwide network (details of which are available on request by emailing or calling us as provided above) for the purposes described above. This may mean that personal data is transferred to countries which do not have laws or regulations which protect personal data as extensively as the United States, where the server for this Website is located. We use reasonable measures to limit the disclosure of the data you provide to us only to certain staff within HipHopStan and its affiliates (i.e. staff whose job it is to process your inquiries and survey answers or otherwise administer the Website, and those staff involved in the provision of HipHopStan services and products which may be of interest to you) and to require that they process the data only for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy.  
  
**Modifications to this Policy**  
  
HipHopStan may make modifications or amendments to this policy from time to time. In the event that such changes alter how HipHopStan gathers, processes, uses or discloses your personally identifiable information, HipHopStan will post such changes on the Website.  
  
**Intellectual Property**  
  
HipHopStan, its suppliers, licensors, or the original creators of all materials on the HipHopStan Website own all copyrightable subject matter on this Website and all trademarks, patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes or other proprietary rights of HipHopStan and/or such other parties. No license to or right in any such copyrights, trademarks, patents, proprietary information, technologies, products, processes and other proprietary rights of HipHopStan and/or other parties is granted to or conferred upon you. In addition, direct linking, deep linking, framing, page-jacking, meta-tagging, and using a robot, spider, or automated device of any kind to monitor or copy our Website is strictly prohibited.  
  
Notwithstanding the foregoing, HipHopStan hereby authorizes you to make and print a limited number of copies of the graphic content of this Website solely for your personal and private use in learning about, evaluating, or acquiring HipHopStan products and services. Except where expressly noted, no other permission is granted to print, copy, reproduce, distribute, transmit, upload, download, store, display in public, alter, or modify the content contained on this Website. Any unauthorized use of any material contained on this Website may violate copyright, trademark or other intellectual property laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and communications regulations and statutes. Any other use of materials on this site, including reproduction for purposes other than those expressly permitted above, modification, distribution or republication, without prior written permission of HipHopStan is strictly prohibited. Any copy made by you as permitted above must retain all copyright and trademark notices, and any other proprietary notices, contained in the materials. The use of such materials on any other website or in any environment of networked computers is prohibited.  
  
**Hypertext Links  
**  
This site contains hypertext links to sites that are not created or maintained by HipHopStan. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website and not to any of these third party Websites. HipHopStan is not responsible for the accuracy, relevance, timeliness, or completeness of those third party sites. The inclusion of any link to such sites does not imply endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation by HipHopStan of those sites. HipHopStan disclaims any liability for links (1) from another website to hiphopstan.com and (2) to another website from hiphopstan.com. HipHopStan cannot guarantee the standards of any website to which links are provided on this Website nor shall HipHopStan be held responsible for the contents of other websites to which this Website is linked or any subsequent links. For this reason, HipHopStan does not represent or warrant that the contents of any third party website is accurate, compliant with state or federal law, or compliant with copyright or other intellectual property laws. HipHopStan does not endorse the contents of these third party websites in any way. Also, HipHopStan is not responsible for web casting or any other form of transmission received from any linked website. Any reliance on the contents of a third party website is done at your own risk and you assume all responsibilities and consequences resulting from such reliance.
